<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--

This is a DTD description of a rules file.  However, since NanoXML that JOGRE
uses doesn't support DTD descriptions, it is given in a comment.

<!DOCTYPE rules [
<!ELEMENT rules (section+)>
<!ATTLIST rules content (text | text/html | text/rtf) "text"
				title CDATA #REQUIRED>
	<!ELEMENT section (section+ | CDATA)>
	<!ATTLIST title CDATA #IMPLIED>
]>

Notes: The "rules" element *must* have a title even though that title is never
       shown to the users.  If the title isn't there, then nothing will display
       in the rules window.

       Sections are not required to have a title, but only sections with titles
       will show up in the index'd tree list.

       NanoXML doesn't support mixing elements and CDATA inside of an element,
       and so non-title'd sections allow that functionality.

       You can embed sections within sections and they will show up in the
       tree as subsections.

       The <![CDATA[ ... ]]> verbiage is needed for text that uses HTML tags within
       it.  Without them, NanoXML would try to parse them as XML and fail.  For plain
       text rules files, you don't need them.
-->

<rules content="text/html" title="Rules">
	<section title="Introduction">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Introduction</u></b></font><br>
		The game of Grand Prix Jumping was designed by Jerry Dziuba.<br><br>
		Many thanks to Jerry for encouraging development of this computer version of his game
		to be made.<br><br>
		The turn highlight buttons are based on drawings by Benji Park and are in the
		public domain and is available from http://www.openclipart.org<br><br>
		The lock that indicates an uneditable board is by AJ Ashton and is in the
		public domain and is available from http://www.openclipart.org<br><br>
		All other graphics drawn by Jerry Dziuba and Richard Walter.<br><br>
		The program was written by Richard Walter (rwalter42@yahoo.com)<br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Overview">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Overview</u></b></font><br>
		In Grand Prix Jumping, the players take on the roles of riders, leading their steeds
		through a Grand Prix competition course that includes fences of varying rail heights,
		as well as a water jump.  Getting through the course fast will help a player's cause
		but will not guarantee victory as the winner is not the horse that finishes faster
		but the one with the fewest fault points.<br><br>
		Players design the course before each game so the strategy of the race changes with
		each race.  Players can make the course as demanding as they want.  While Grand Prix
		Jumping is at it heart a card game, there is very little luck involved, and the better
		rider will be victorious.  Now saddle up and hit the course...<br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Components">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Components</u></b></font><br>
		There is a deck of 80 playing cards.<br>
		There is a course layout board of 48 spaces.<br>
		There are two horse & rider tokens - one for each player.<br>
		There are jumps with rail heights of 1-5 rails and water jumps four spaces long.<br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Playing the Game">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Playing the Game</u></b></font><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Overview">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Overview</u></b></font><br>
			In Grand Prix Jumping, players use cards to move their horses and riders
			around the track and over the jumps.  Cards are distributed via a "divide
			and choose" method where one player will divide cards into two piles and
			the other player will choose which pile to take and which to lave for
			the divider to use.  After the split each player can play cards to move
			their horses around the course.  Then they verify that they are not over
			the allowable hand limit size.  Fault points are accumulated during the game
			and are the ultimate victory condition.  The player finishing with the fewer
			fault points is the victor and may or may not be the rider crossing the
			finish line first.<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Preparation">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Preparation</u></b></font><br>
			The track board is set up with the two player's horses on the first space.
			The jumps are placed however the players wish.<br><br>
			When the game is started, the creator picks an initial layout of jumps to use.
			Once both players have started the game, the game enters an editing phase where
			either player may change the layout of fences on the board.  Clicking on a space
			on the board will increase the height of the fence on that space by one rail.
			Holding the <shift> key and clicking on a space will decrease the height of
			the fence on that space by one rail.  Water fences are placed by clicking on
			a height 5 fence, if valid.  It is not allowed to place fences on a water fence
			or to have water fences overlap.<br><br>
			When a player is done making edits, he must click the "Done" button.  If the
			opponent, however, makes any edits after that point, then the first player's
			done button will become active again and the player must click it again to
			show acceptance of the new layout.  Once both players have indicated that they
			accept the layout without any intervening changes, then the initial cards
			are played from the draw pile and play begins.<br><br>
			When the table is created, the creator may elect to not allow edits to be
			made to the board.  In this case, a lock icon is shown in the dividing area
			to indicate that no edits are allowed and the game will skip the editing
			phase and go right to dealing cards when both players start.<br>
			]]>
		</section>

		<section title="The Split">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>The Split</u></b></font><br>
			For each round of play, one player will be the divider and the other will be
			the chooser.  The players alternate each round with the divider of the current
			round becoming the chooser for the next round, etc...  Player 0 is the initial
			divider.<br><br>
			The divider is given seven cards face up.  He must then split the seven cards
			into two groups.  He may split them in any way he wants as long as there is
			at least one card in each group.  That is the only requirement for how the
			cards are divided up.<br><br>
			Once the divider has signaled that the split is done, his opponent (the chooser)
			decides which of the two groups to take and the divider gets the group that the
			chooser did not pick.  All "playable cards" are placed into the player's hands
			and are hidden from the other player.  "Immediate action" cards are left face-up
			in front of the players, as these must be settled before the end of their current turn.<br><br>
			Once the chooser has completed any movement he is able to make and has used all
			of the action cards he has in front of him, his turn for this round is concluded.
			At this time, he must make sure that he is not over his allowed hand limit.  If he
			is, then he must discard down to the limit.<br><br>
			It is then the divider's turn to use the cards left to him by the chooser.  At the
			end of his turn, he must also be sure he is within his current allowable hand limit.<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Explanation of Cards - Hand cards">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Hand Cards</u></b></font><br>
			<i>Hand cards may be held in a player's hand and played in that turn or future rounds</i><br><br>
			<b>Height card</b><br>
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;These cards are used to get the height required to clear a jump.
				The number on the card corresponds to the number of rungs your horse can clear on any given
				jump.  For example, a height card of 4 will allow your horse to clear a 1, 2, 3 or 4 rung jump.<br><br>
			<b>Length card</b><br>
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;These cards are used to give your horse the required length
				to clear jumps.  At a minimum you'll need a length of two to clear any vertical
				jumps, assuming you are beginning the jump directly in front of the jump.  A
				minimum length of five is needed to clear the water jump.<br><br>
			<b>Canter card</b><br>
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Canter cards allow you to move your horse between the jumps.
				You move your horse the corresponding number of spaces as the number on the Canter card(s) played.<br><br>
			<b>Saddle card</b><br>
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A saddle card is required to play any of the movement cards (jump or canter).
				For each saddle card played you are allowed to play one set of jump cards and/or canter cards.
				You may play any number of cards, but once you change from either cantering or jumping you
				can't play more of those types of cards unless you play another saddle card.<br>
				<i>Example: A player plays a saddle card to start moving, followed by two "canter 1" cards to
				move his horse forward 2 spaces.  He then plays a combination of jump cards equal to
				3 height and 2 width to clear a 3 high jump.  If he wishes to continue cantering from this
				point, he would need to play another saddle card.</i><br><br>
			<b>Ribbon card</b><br>
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ribbon cards allow you to rely on your past accomplishments.
				As such, you can play a ribbon card and either reduce your fault count by 1/4 point or
				use it to trade in for another card from the deck.  If the card you get is an Immediate
				action card, then you must use it this turn, otherwise the card will be put into your
				hand.<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Explanation of Cards - Immediate Action cards">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Immediate Action Cards</u></b></font><br>
			<i>Immediate action cards must be used in the same turn as acquired and cannot be held for future turns.</i><br><br>
			<b>Stable card</b><br>
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Stable cards increase the number of cards a player may hold in his hand by 1.
				The beginning hand limit for each player is eight cards (enforced at the end of their turn.)
				Stable cards are not recycled into the discard deck.<br><br>
			<b> Fault cards</b><br>
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;These cards penalize the player with fault points.  The player gets
				the appropriate number of fault points.<br><br>
			<b>Dual Rider card</b><br>
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;This card allows the player to draw two cards from the top of the draw pile
				and, after looking at them, decide which to keep himself and which to give to his opponent.
				If you have already taken your turn for this round and receive an immediate action card from
				your opponent, then you must satisfy that card before the end of the round, but you may not
				take another "normal turn" in the process.  If you have already taken your turn for this round
				and receive a hand card from your opponent, then it goes into your hand.  You do not have to
				discard down to your hand limit until at the end of your next "normal" turn.<br><br>
			<b>Race Official card</b><br>
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;If you receive this card your horse has failed a vet check.  As a
				penalty you must either take one full fault point or discard half of your hand cards - rounded
				up.  <i>(If you have 7 cards, you must discard 4)</i>.  You can choose when during your turn to
				apply the Race Official card, so you may play cards during your "normal" turn before having
				to discard half of them, if you choose that option.<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Clearing Jumps">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Clearing Jumps</u></b></font><br>
			To clear a jump, height and length cards are played in combination.  You must play
			enough height cards to equal or exceed the number of rails for a jump and, at the
			same time, also play enough length cards to carry your horse to the space beyond
			the jump.  The space the jump is on counts as one so the minimum value of length
			cards needed to clear a jump would be two, assuming that the horse began the jump
			in the space directly in front of the jump.<br><br>
			You may use any combination of height and length cards with the two restrictions:<br><br>
			1) Height and length cards may only be used when going over a jump.  You may use
			the length of the jump to clear more space ahead of or beyond a jump, but under no
			circumstances may you use a jump to simply move forward in lieu of canter cards.<br><br>
			2) You card combination cannot exceed a value of seven.<br>
			<i>(Example: You could <b>not</b> use a height of 5 and a length of 3.  Therefore, to
			clear a 5-rail jump cleanly, you must begin your movement directly in front of the jump
			and play cards equal to 5 in height and 2 in length.)</i><br><br>
			Note: A height card is required to clear the water jump with no faults, but any value will work.<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Fault Points">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Fault Points</u></b></font><br>
			Throughout the game, players will accumulate fault points.  There are three different
			ways a player can be penalized fault points:<br><br>
			1) Fault Cards<br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The player gets as many points as listed on the card.<br><br>
			2) Race Official Card<br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;If a player does not want to lose half of his cards, he is penalized
			one full fault point.<br><br>
			3) Not clearing a jump<br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A player may purposely not play enough jump points to clear a jump.
			For each rail not cleared, then player is penalized one full fault point.<br>
			For the water jump, players are penalized for coming up short length-wise.  For each space
			short, they are penalized one full fault point.<br><br>
			The maximum amount of fault points a player may have is four.  If a player goes over the
			limit of four faults, he is immediately disqualified and loses the game!  The only way
			to reduce your fault points is through the use of the Ribbon cards to reduce your fault
			total by 1/4 point per each Ribbon card played.  If both players should happen to go over
			the four point limit during the same turn, then the player with the fewer fault points
			is the winner.  If both players are tied, then the player whose horse is further along
			the track is the winner.  If both players are on the same space, then the game is a tie.<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Ending the Game">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Ending the Game</u></b></font><br>
			The game ends when, after a full round, either one (or both) players has more than
			four full fault points, or when either one (or both) players has their horse on
			the last, checkered, space of the board.  If the other player's horse is still on
			the course, he is penalized 1/4 fault point for each space he is behind as a
			time penalty.  <i>(The amount of penalty fault points to assign is shown on the board.)</i>
			The player with the fewer fault points is the winner!  If both players are tied, then
			the player whose horse made it to the finish space is the winner.  If both horses
			are on the same space and both players have equal fault points, then the game is a tie.<br>]]>
		</section>
	</section>

	<section title="Interface Details">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Interface Details</u></b></font><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Starting a New Game">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Starting a New Game</u></b></font><br>
			When you start a new game, there are several options you must choose from
			to configure the game.<br><br>
			<b>Initial jump layout</b> - Choose the initial placement of the jumps on the board.
			Selecting "Random" will build a random board.  Selecting "Use Code" will use the
			code entered in the text box below.  Selecting any other entry will use that
			layout.<br>
			<b>Initial track code</b> - If the "Use Code" option is selected for the
			initial layout, then the code entered in this box will be used for the initial layout.
			<b>Open Hands</b> - If enabled, then both players will be able to see their opponent's cards.<br>
			<b>Enable Editing</b> - If enabled, the players may modify the jumps on the board before the
			card play begins.  If disabled, the board is locked to the initial placement of jumps.<br><br>
			When selecting a random initial layout, the random track will have the following
			properties:<br>
			1) There are always at least 1 space between fences.  (ie: there is never an "oxer" jump)<br>
			2) There are always two fences of height 1, 2 & 3 and a single fence of heights 4 & 5.<br>
			3) There is always a single water jump and it is located on the 2nd or 3rd row of the board.<br>
			4) There is always an empty space before and after the water jump.<br><br>
			After the board setup is complete, the code for the current setup is
			displayed in the chat window.  This code may be entered in the code window
			to set the fences back to this configuration again.<br>
			]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Fault Point Panel">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Fault Point Panel</u></b></font><br>
			At the top left corner is the fault point panel.  This shows the number of
			fault points that each player has accumulated.  As fault points are gained,
			the bar will fill in with that player's color.  When a player goes over the
			maximum of four full fault points, the bar will wrap around back to the left
			side and start filling in in red.<br><br>
			Clicking in the fault window will bring up a dialog box with a summary of
			the scoring for each player.  This allows players to determine where their
			fault points came from.<br><br>
			<b>Note:</b> Currently, this dialog box displays the
			summary for that time in the game.  It will <i>not</i> update automatically as
			new fault points are accrued.  The dialog box must be closed and a new
			one opened to get an up-to-date list.  Also, spectators joining a game
			in progress will <i>not</i> see any history for prior to the time when
			they joined the game.<br>
			]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Done Button">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Done Button</u></b></font><br>
			Below the fault point panel is the done button.  Players must press the
			done button to indicate that they are done with their turn.  The text of
			the done button will change to indicate the action that will occur when
			the button is pressed.  If the button is disabled, then it is not legal
			to end the turn at that point.  This is usually caused by having immediate
			action cards that haven't been played yet.<br>
			]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Dividing Panel">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Dividing Panel</u></b></font><br>
			Below the Done Button is the dividing panel.  As each round begins,
			seven cards will be placed in the left side of the dividing panel.  The
			player that is the divider for this turn will divide the cards into
			two groups, one on the left and one on the right.  Moving the mouse
			over the groups will show which card will move when clicked on.<br><br>
			When the divider is done dividing the cards, he should press the Done
			Button to indicate that dividing is finished.<br><br>
			After the divider has finished his action, the chooser must now decide
			which pile he will take and which he will leave for the divider.  Mousing
			over the groups will outline one of the groups.  Clicking on a highlighted
			group will cause the chooser to get those cards and the divider to get
			the group not chosen.<br><br>
			The player who is to take the next action is shown by the horse in the
			lower left corner of the Dividing Panel.<br>
			]]>
		</section>

		<section title="State Panel">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>State Panel</u></b></font><br>
			The lower left corner of the table shows a text panel that indicates what the current
			state of the game is and whose turn it is.<br><br>
			This also indicates that number
			of cards in the draw pile.  When this number hits 0, then the discard pile
			is reshuffled and becomes the new draw pile.  A chat message is also displayed
			that indicates that the reshuffle occurred.<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Hand Panel">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Hand Panel</u></b></font><br>
			The top of the window shows your hand.  Moving the mouse over a card will cause
			it to move up a little to show which card is being pointed at.  Only cards
			which are legal to play at any given time will respond this way to the mouse.
			Clicking the mouse will select the current card and play it.<br><br>
			Hand cards appear on the left side of the hand panel and are kept sorted.<br><br>
			Immediate action cards appear on the right side of the hand panel and are kept
			in the order in which they are received during the current round.<br><br>
			A box is placed to show what your current hand limit is and how many cards
			you currently have.  The box is placed such that it aligns with the left
			edge of the last card that you are allowed to keep in your hand.  As
			Stable cards are drawn, the box will move to the right.<br><br>
			When it is your turn to play, your horse will be shown in the lower left
			corner of your Hand Panel.<br><br>
			When Saddle, Canter, Height and Length cards are played, they are darkened
			and an icon representing them is placed on the game board to show where they
			will be applied.  Clicking on a darkened card will un-play the card and
			move it back into the player's hand.  Note that un-playing a saddle card
			will also un-play any Canter, Height and/or Length cards that follow that
			Saddle card.  Cards must be played from the hand in the order that they
			will be applied toward movement.  This means, for example, that the
			first movement card selected must be a Saddle card to start the movement.
			After that, either a Canter, Height or Length card can be played.<br><br>
			When a Ribbon card is clicked on, the player will have to choose whether
			to apply the card to reduce the fault points by 1/4 point or to trade it
			in for another card.  Click on the appropriate half of the card to take
			the action.  Clicking outside of the card will cancel the selection and
			put the ribbon card back into the player's hand.<br><br>
			The results of Stable and Fault cards are immediately applied by the game
			when drawn and will always show up in the Immediate Card area darkened.<br><br>
			When a Race Official card is clicked on, the player will have to choose
			whether to receive one full fault point or to discard half his hand.
			Click on the appropriate half of the card to take the action.  Clicking
			outside of the card will cancel the selection and put the Race Official
			card back into the player's hand.<br><br>
			When a Dual Rider card is clicked on, the Immediate action cards will be
			replaced by a display of the next two top cards of the deck.  The player
			must choose one of these two cards for himself by clicking in it.  The
			other card will be given to his opponent.  There is no way to undo clicking
			on the Dual Rider card.<br><br>
			When it is a player's turn, his horse will be shown along with a highlight
			button in the lower left corner of the hand panel.<br><br>
			]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Main Board">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Main Board</u></b></font><br>
			In the center of the table is the main board.  This shows the current
			positions of the horses and the jumps.<br><br>
			As you play movement cards from your hand, small icons will be placed
			on the main board to show where those cards will be applied.  To remove
			a card and put it back into his hand, a player may either click on the
			darkened card in the Hand panel, or click on the small icon on the track.<br><br>
			As movement cards are applied, a line is drawn to show the horse's progress
			along the track.  If the current sequence of cards is a legal play, then a
			shadow horse is drawn at the end of the line.  If the current sequence of cards
			is <b>not</b> a legal play, then the line will just end with a dot.<br><br>
			If the current sequence of cards is a legal play that ends with jump cards,
			then a small "+" icon will appear by the shadow horse.  Clicking on the "+"
			will place a fake saddle on the board and allow another jump to start.  In
			this way, multiple jumps, each of which is limited to a total value of 7
			can be played by one saddle card.<br><br>
			If you remove a fake saddle card by clicking on it's icon, then the jump
			and canter cards of just that jump are removed as well.  If you remove a
			real saddle card, then all of the subsequent fake saddles coming after
			that are removed as well.<br><br>
			When a player is ready to commit to moving his horse, he must click on the
			shadow horse shown on the board.  This will take all of the cards played
			on the current turn and remove them from the player's hand and move the horse
			to the target location.<br><br>
			While a player is building a jump, the opponent (and spectators) will only
			see the location of the shadow horse as it moves along the track.  The
			opponent and spectators only see the actual cards played when the move is
			committed.<br><br>
			When jump is made over a fence that does not clear the jump, a warning sign
			is placed near the jump indicating how many fault points will be accrued
			by the player if the jump were to be committed.  These warning signs
			cannot be removed by clicking on them.  They are removed by adding additional
			height (or, in the case of a water jump, length) cards to overcome the fence.<br><br>
			While a game is not in progress, if editing is disabled, then a lock icon
			is shown in the middle of the board.<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Opponent Hand Panel">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Opponent Hand Panel</u></b></font><br>
			Below the track is the Opponent's Hand Panel.  This shows the cards for
			your opponent's Hand and Immediate cards.<br><br>
			If the game is being played open handed, then you can see your opponent's
			hand cards.  Otherwise all you will see is the backs.<br><br>
			The opponent's Immediate cards are always shown face up.<br>
			]]>
		</section>
	</section>

	<section title="Customization">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Customization</u></b></font><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section>
			<![CDATA[
			The Grand Prix Jumping game allows a fair amount of customization for
			the client.<br>
			Most of the customization is done via the game.properties file.<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Initial Layouts">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Initial Layouts</u></b></font><br>
			Information about the initial layout of jumps on the track is read from
			a local XML file.  The file to use is specified in the games.properties
			file as the <b>layout.filename</b> property.  This file can be edited
			by any text editing program.<br><br>
			The file can contain multiple initial layouts to choose from when a new
			game is started.
			]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Customizing Images">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Customizing Images</u></b></font><br>
			The images are stored in the images directory.  Each image has an entry
			in the game.properties file that points to it.  You can change/edit any
			of the images and change the entry in game.properties.  Some images have
			an array of pictures with each picture being identical in size.
			If you edit such a file, you can change the size of each element, but make
			sure that you keep the array structure.<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="games.properties File">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>games.properties File</u></b></font><br>
			There are several properties in the games.properties file that can be
			used to customize the view of the local client.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>layout.filename</b> - This is the XML file that
			contains the initial layouts provided when a new game is started.  The
			file is only read by the game and can be modified by the user.  Only
			the creator of a game needs to have a copy of the layout used.  The other
			players and spectators will get the initial layout from the creator.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>preferences.defaultOpenHands</b> - This sets the default
			setting of the "open hands" check box when starting a new game.  Set to 1
			to set the check box.  Any other value disables the checkbox.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>preferences.defaultAllowEdits</b> - This sets the default
			setting of the "Allow Edits" check box when starting a new game.  Set to 1
			to set the check box.  Any other value disables the checkbox.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>hand.selected.vertical.offset</b> - The number of
			pixels to offset the card when deciding which card to choose from your
			hand.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>hand.card.spacing</b> - The number of pixels of
			overlap between cards in your hand.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>sort.card.spacing</b> - The number of pixels of
			vertical overlap between cards in the Dividing Panel.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>sort.selected.horiz.offset</b> - The number of pixels
			to offset the card when deciding which card to move from one group to
			the other during dividing.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>sort.well.spacing</b> - The number of pixels
			between the two groups in the Dividing Panel.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>sort.border.size</b> - The number of pixels of border
			space to put around the card groups in the Dividing Panel.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>sort.outline.thickness</b> - The number of pixels in
			the outline to use when choosing which group of cards to take from
			the Dividing Panel.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>faults.overflow.colour</b> - This is the color
			to use to fill in the fault bar when it loops back around past four
			fault points.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>fault.therm.height</b> - The number of pixels tall
			the fault thermometers are.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>fault.therm.pointSpread</b> - The number of pixels
			to put between each 1/4 point in the fault thermometers.<br><br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;<b>turn.highlight.index</b> - The image file that is
			used to display the highlight button that shows behind the horse in the
			hand areas to indicate which player's turn it is contains four potential
			images to use as the highlight.  This number should be set to a number
			between 0 and 3 to select which of the four highlight buttons should be
			used.  Any other value will result in no highlighting behind the horses.<br><br>
			]]>
		</section>
	</section>
</rules>
