<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--

This is A DTD description of a rules file.  However, since NanoXML that JOGRE
uses doesn't support DTD descriptions, it is given in a comment.

<!DOCTYPE rules [
<!ELEMENT rules (section+)>
<!ATTLIST rules content (text | text/html | text/rtf) "text"
				title CDATA #REQUIRED>
	<!ELEMENT section (section+ | CDATA)>
	<!ATTLIST title CDATA #IMPLIED>
]>

Notes: The "rules" element *must* have a title even though that title is never
       shown to the users.  If the title isn't there, then nothing will display
       in the rules window.

       Sections are not required to have a title, but only sections with titles
       will show up in the index'd tree list.

       NanoXML doesn't support mixing elements and CDATA inside of an element,
       and so non-title'd sections allow that functionality.

       You can embed sections within sections and they will show up in the
       tree as subsections.

       The <![CDATA[ ... ]]> verbiage is needed for text that uses HTML tags within
       it.  Without them, NanoXML would try to parse them as XML and fail.  For plain
       text rules files, you don't need them.
-->

<rules content="text/html" title="Rules">
	<section title="Introduction">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Introduction</u></b></font><br>
		The game of Ninety Nine was designed by David Parlett.<br>
		It is described in the book "Original Card Games".<br><br>
		The card images used in the game were drawn by Nicu Buculei.  They are in the
		public domain and are available from http://www.openclipart.org/<br><br>
		The card suit images used to indicate the trump suit were drawn by Guillaume Boitel.  They are
		in the public domain and are available from http://www.openclipart.org/<br><br>
		The program was written by Richard Walter (rwalter42@yahoo.com)<br><br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Overview">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Overview</u></b></font><br>
		Ninety Nine is a card game for 3 players.<br><br>
		Players bid for an exact number of tricks to be taken using cards
		from their hands to make the bid.<br><br>
		There are premium bids available that provide bonus points for a player
		who succesfully makes his bid.  But the bonus points will go to <i>both</i>
		of the other two players if they prevent the premium bidder from
		succesfully completing his bid.<br><br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Deck">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Deck</u></b></font><br>
		Ninety Nine is played with a deck of 36 cards using only the cards 6 through Ace.<br><br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Playing the Game">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Playing the Game</u></b></font><br>
			A game of Ninety Nine consists of 3, 6 or 9 rounds.  A round consists
			of a deal of the cards, followed by bidding, trick taking and then scoring.<br><br>
			At the end of each round, the dealer rotates to the left.  That means
			that each player is dealer the same number of times in a game.<br><br>
			After all of the rounds of the game, the player with the highest total score
			is the winner.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Dealing">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Dealing</u></b></font><br>
			The 36 cards are shuffled and dealt out with each player getting 12.<br><br>
			A trump suit is determined randomly.<br><br>
			Note: If playing with real cards, add
			a joker to the deck. After dealing the 12 cards to each player, the
			37th card is turned up to determine the trump suit.  The joker assumes
			the identity of the turned-up card for this round.  If the turned up card
			is the joker, then the round is played with no trump.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Bidding">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Bidding</u></b></font><br>
			Each player will choose 3 cards from their hand to be set aside as their
			bid.  After choosing thier bid cards, each player will have 9 cards remaining
			to use during the trick taking.  Bids remain secret from the other players
			until all the tricks have been played (except in the case of premium bids (see below)).<br><br>
			The bid cards represent the number of tricks to be taken (between 0 and 9) by adding
			the <b><i>suits</i></b> as follows:<br>
			<ul>
			<li>Diamond means 0 tricks</li>
			<li>Spade means 1 trick</li>
			<li>Heart means 2 tricks</li>
			<li>Clubs means 3 tricks</li>
			</ul>
			For example, if a player's bid cards were two spades and a heart, then the bid
			would be 1 + 1 + 2 = 4 tricks.<br><br>
			The values of the bid cards are not important, only their suits.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Premium Bids">
			<section>
				<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Premium Bids</u></b></font><br>
				Premium bids allow a player to attempt to win bonus points.  If a player makes
				a premium bid and successfully takes the number of tricks bid then he will
				get bonus points.  However, if a player makes a premium bid and does not take
				the number of tricks bid, then <i>both</i> of the other two players will get the bonus
				points.<br><br>
				There are two premium bids available: Declaration and Revelation.<br><br>]]>
			</section>
			
			<section title="Declaration">
				<![CDATA[<b><u>Declaration</u></b><br>
				A player who declares will turn his bid cards face up so the other two players
				will know how many tricks the declarer is attempting to take.<br><br>]]>
			</section>

			<section title="Revelation">
				<![CDATA[<b><u>Revelation</u></b><br>
				A player who reveals will turn both his bid cards <i><b>and</b></i> his entire playing
				hand face up.  This allows the other two players to know both how many
				tricks the revealer is attempting to take and what cards he has to do it.<br><br>
				To make this easier, a player who reveals can choose which player should
				lead the first card of the round (including himself) and also doesn't have
				to show his hand until after the first card is led.<br><br>]]>
			</section>

			<section title="Premium Bid Priority">
				<![CDATA[<b><u>Premium Bid Priority</u></b><br>
				Only one player may be playing a premium bid in any one round.  The player
				to the left of the dealer has first option to make a premium bid.  If that
				player declines, then the player to his left has the option.  If the second
				player also declines, then the dealer has a chance.<br><br>
				If a player has bid to declare, then a following player can over-bid to
				reveal.  In this case, the declarer has the option to increase his bid to
				a revelation or to yield to the player who just over-bid.<br><br>]]>
			</section>
		</section>

		<section title="Card Play">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Card Play</u></b></font><br>
			If there is a player who bid a revelation, then that player chooses who is
			to lead the first card.  Otherwise, the player to the left of the dealer
			leads the first card.<br><br>
			A player can lead any card from his hand.  A player must follow the suit of the
			lead card if he can.  If a player has no cards of the lead suit, then he can
			play any card.  A player is not obligated to play a trump suit (unless trump is
			the lead suit.)<br><br>
			Tricks are won by the highest card of the lead suit or the highest trump, 
			if one is played.<br><br>
			The winner of a trick leads to the next one.<br><br>
			After all 9 tricks have been played, the round is scored.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Scoring">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Scoring</u></b></font><br>
			Each player's score is made up of three parts:  a score for the tricks actually
			taken, a bonus for taking the exact number of tricks as bid, and a bonus
			for succeeding or preventing a premium bid.<br><br>
			<b>Tricks Taken</b><br>
			A player scores 1 point for each trick taken.<br><br>
			<b>Bid Bonus</b><br>
			If all three players met their bid exactly, then each gets 10 bonus points.<br>
			If two players met their bid exactly, then those two each get 20 bonus points.<br>
			If one player met his bid exactly, then that player gets 30 bonus points.<br><br>
			<b>Premium Bonus</b><br>
			If a player bid a declaration and met his bid, then that player gets 30 bonus points.<br>
			If a player bid a declaration and did not meet his bid, then the other two players get
			30 bonus points each.<br>
			If a player bid a revelation and met his bid, then that player get 60 bonus points.<br>
			If a player bid a revelation and did not meet his bid, then the other two players get
			60 bonus points each.<br><br>
			Scores for each round are summed to provide a total score.<br><br>]]>
		</section>
	</section>

	<section title="Interface Details">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Interface Details</u></b></font><br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Starting a New Game">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Starting a New Game</u></b></font><br>
			When you start a new game, you must choose the number of rounds in the
			game, either 3, 6, or 9.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Screen Layout">
			<section>
				<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Screen Layout</u></b></font><br><br>]]>
			</section>

			<section title="Card Panels">
				<![CDATA[<b><u>Card Panels</u></b><br>
				There are three rows of card areas; one for each player.  You are always the
				top player, with the following players moving down in order.<br><br>
				Within each row,<br>
				<ul>
				<li>The left most group of cards are the bid cards.</li>
				<li>The next group of cards are the hands.  The cards in the hands are kept
					sorted by suit and value.</li>
				<li>The next area shows the cards as they are played on the trick.
					This area also contains the buttons used to make bids during bid time.</li>
				<li>The right most group indicate the tricks taken during a round.</li>
				</ul><br>]]>
			</section>

			<section title="Score Panel">
				<![CDATA[<b><u>Score Panel</u></b><br>
				At the bottom of the window is the score panel.<br><br>
				There is a column for each round of the game, showing which
				suit was trump and each player's score for that round.<br><br>
				The far right column is the total score for each player.<br><br>]]>
			</section>
		</section>

		<section title="Bidding">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Bidding</u></b></font><br>
			After the cards have been dealt, you need to make your bid.  The trump suit
			for the round is shown in the score panel.<br><br>
			Selecting a card from your hand will move it to the bid area.  Selecting a card
			from the bid area will move it back into your hand.  As you move cards into the
			bid area, the current value of the bid will be updated in the bid button.<br><br>
			When you have three cards in the bid area, then the bid buttons will become
			enabled.  Clicking on one of the bid buttons will submit your bid to the server
			and will lock in your bid.<br><br>
			Selecting the top bid button will result in a normal bid being made.  Selecting
			the second bid button will indicate to the server that you wish to make a declaration
			bid.  Selecting the third bid button will indicate to the server that you wish
			to make a revelation bid and will result in three more buttons to allow you to
			choose which player you want to lead the first card.<br><br>
			Once all of the players have bid, then the server will determine which premium bid,
			if any, has the priority and will be played that hand.  If you make a premium bid
			which is not accepted because some other player with higher priority made one,
			then your attempt to make a priority bid is <i>not</i> revealed to the other players.<br><br>
			If you bid to declare and had priority over a player that bid reveal, then a dialog
			box will ask if you wish to upgrade your bid to a reveal or not.  In this one
			instance, the other players will be informed that you had been asked the question
			and your response.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Trick Taking">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Trick Taking</u></b></font><br>
			During trick taking, the player who is to play the next card will have a yellow
			card outline displayed.<br><br>
			When it is your time to play, select a card from your hand to play it.
			Only cards that are legal to play will move up when moused over.<br><br>
			When all three cards have been played on a trick, they will be moved into the
			taken card area of the player who played the highest card.  The cards of the
			most recent trick are placed face-up for display.  Tricks previously taken are
			grouped and placed face down.<br><br>]]>
		</section>
	</section>

	<section title="Customization">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Customization</u></b></font><br>
			Many parameters of the game are cusomizable from the game.properties file.
			This file is editable with any text editor.<br><br>
			<i>player.colour.x</i> - Can be used to change the color of the players.<br><br>
			<i>display.hand.cardSpacing</i> - The number of pixels between left-hand edges
			of two cards in the hand that are of the same suit.<br><br>
			<i>display.hand.suitSpacing</i> - The number of pixels between left-hand edges
			of two cards in the hand that are of different suits.<br><br>
			<i>display.hand.selectYOffset</i> - The number of pixels to move a selectable
			card when moused over.<br><br>
			<i>display.taken.cardSpacing</i> - The number of pixels between left-hand edges
			of cards in the taken tricks area.<br><br>
			<i>display score.digitSpacing</i> - The number of pixels between digits of multi-digit
			numbers in the score area.<br><br>
			<i>display.score.HSpacing</i> - The number of pixels between each column of the score
			panel<br><br>
			<i>display.score.VSpacing</i> - The number of pixels between each row of the score panel.<br><br>
			<i>display.cardback</i> - Chooses which card back to use.  Image.2 contains a number
			of images of card backs.  If this value is set to a number from 0 to (n-1), where n is
			the number of card back images in image.2, then that card back is used in the game.
			If this value is set to the string "random", then a card back is chosen randomly for
			each round of the game.  If this value is set to the string "rotate", then the card back
			will start at the first one and then move onto the next one for each round of the game,
			rotating back to the first after all have been used.  See the section below for more
			details on customizing images.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Customizing Images">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Customizing Images</u></b></font><br>
			The game.properties file contains entries for images used in the game.  You can
			customize the game by making new image files and setting the appropriate image.x
			line in the game.properties file to point to your new image.<br><br>
			Each image line contains a filename followed by a size.  If you change an image
			file, make sure that you change the size as well.<br><br>
			<i>image.0</i> - The icon used in the window.  This must be 16x16 pixels.<br><br>
			<i>image.1</i> - The cards used in the game.  This is an array of images of the
			cards.  You can change the size of the cards, but each card must be the same size
			and the cards must remain in the same relative position.  (ie: the 6 of diamonds
			must be in the upper left corner, with the 6 of spades below it.).<br>
			If you change the size of the cards, you must also change the card backs and the
			card prompt images to be the same size as the card faces.<br><br>
			<i>image.2</i> - The card backs.  This is a horizontal row of card backs.  Each
			card back must be the same size as a card in image.1.  You can add as many card
			backs as you like, and use the <i>display.cardback</i> property to select which
			is used in the game.<br><br>
			<i>image.3</i> - The symbols used to indicate the trump suit in the score panel.
			This is a horizontal row of 5 symbols, one each for No Trump, Diamonds, Spades,
			Hearts and Clubs.<br><br>
			<i>image.4</i> - The digits used to draw the scores.<br><br>
			<i>image.5</i> - The prompt used to indicate which player should play next.
			This must be the same size as a card in image.1.<br><br>]]>
		</section>
	</section>
</rules>
