<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--

This is a DTD description of a rules file.  However, since NanoXML that JOGRE
uses doesn't support DTD descriptions, it is given in a comment.

<!DOCTYPE rules [
<!ELEMENT rules (section+)>
<!ATTLIST rules content (text | text/html | text/rtf) "text"
				title CDATA #REQUIRED>
	<!ELEMENT section (section+ | CDATA)>
	<!ATTLIST title CDATA #IMPLIED>
]>

Notes: The "rules" element *must* have a title even though that title is never
       shown to the users.  If the title isn't there, then nothing will display
       in the rules window.

       Sections are not required to have a title, but only sections with titles
       will show up in the index'd tree list.

       NanoXML doesn't support mixing elements and CDATA inside of an element,
       and so non-title'd sections allow that functionality.

       You can embed sections within sections and they will show up in the
       tree as subsections.

       The <![CDATA[ ... ]]> verbiage is needed for text that uses HTML tags within
       it.  Without them, NanoXML would try to parse them as XML and fail.  For plain
       text rules files, you don't need them.
-->
<rules content="text/html" title="Rules">
	<section title="Credits">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Credits</u></b></font><br>
		<b>Warwick the Kingmaker</b> was designed by Tunc Iper.<br><br>
		Many thanks to Tunc and IZ Games for allowing development of this
		computer version of his game to be made.<br><br>
		More information on this and other games is available at
		http://www.izgames.vze.com, including a complete do-it-yourself kit for
		making your own real-life <b>Warwick the Kingmaker</b> game.  At that
		web site is also a complete rule sheet (with much better pictures
		than I can draw) from which these rules were taken.<br><br>
		The main board image was drawn by Tunc Iper and permission for use in
		this game has been granted by him.<br><br>
		The rose picture was developed by Paul Nylander.  It was rendered by
		POV-Ray from source files available at http://www.bugman123.com/Math/Rose.zip<br><br>
		All other graphics drawn by Richard Walter and are put into the public
		domain.<br><br>
		The program was written by Richard Walter (rwalter42@yahoo.com)]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Introduction">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Introduction</u></b></font><br>
		Richard Neville, known as "Warwick the Kingmaker", was a leading
		figure in the Wars of the Roses, during which he helped depose the
		Lancastrian King Henry VI in favor of the Yorkist King Edward IV.
		This earned him his nickname of "the Kingmaker" but he later fell out
		with Edward and restored Henry VI to the throne.  During this period
		Warwick was the richest man in the country outside of the Royal Family
		and was considered the real ruler of England.<br><br>
		"Kingmaker", while a term originally applied to the activities of Richard
		Neville, has come to be applied more generally to a person or group
		that has great influence in a royal or polticial succession, without
		being a viable candidate.  Kingmakers may use political, monetary,
		religious, and/or military means to interfere in the succession.
		<br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Overview">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Overview</u></b></font><br>
		<b>Warwick the Kingmaker</b> is a game for three to five players in
		which you and your opponents play feuding lords trying to get the most
		prestigious status in the realm.  Since your royal family is not a
		viable candidate for the throne you must invest your resources to the
		right candidate for the succession.<br><br>
		The victor is the player with the most prestige points at the end of
		the game.  A player earns prestige points in two ways: by the actions
		of his own house and by supporting another candidate house.  At the
		beginning of each turn, a player can change the candidate that he
		supports as he sees fit.
		<br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Components">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Components</u></b></font><br>
		The main board is divided into four sections, labeled 1, 2, 3 and 4.<br>
		Each player receives three tokens that will be placed on the board.<br>
		Each player also receives a scoring token that is used to keep track
		of the prestige points gained during the game.
		<br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Playing the Game">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Playing the Game</u></b></font><br>
			The game is divided into turns.  The number of turns in a game is
			equal to the number of players in the game.<br>
			Each turn is divided into a single selection phase, followed by
			three rounds of playing tokens.<br>
			After all of the turns in the game are complete, the player with the
			highest total number of prestige points is the winner.
			<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="The Selection Phase">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>The Selection Phase</u></b></font><br>
			At the beginning of each turn, each player secretly chooses one of
			the other players to support during this turn.  This is the secret
			support that you provide as the kingmaker.  A player may not
			choose himself for his secret support.<br><br>
			Once all players have selected their player to support, the game
			enters the placement rounds.
			<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Placement Rounds">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Placement Rounds</u></b></font><br>
			Placment rounds begin with the player who is in the seat that
			corresponds to the turn number.  i.e.: On the first turn, the first
			player will place first.  On the second turn, the second player will
			place first, etc.  Thus, each player will have gone first once in
			each game.<br><br>
			When it is a player's turn in a round, the player must:<br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;1) Place one of his tokens on the board.<br>
			and then<br>
			&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;2) Move any token on the board one quarter clockwise.<br>
			Note that <b><i>any</i></b> token on the board may be moved
			clockwise, not just tokens that belong to the player whose turn it is.<br><br>
			Placement and moving continues until all players have placed all three
			of their tokens on the board.  At this point, the board is scored.
			<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Scoring">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Scoring</u></b></font><br>
			After all players have placed all of their tokens on the board, each
			player reveals which other player they chose for their secret support
			and scoring is done.<br><br>
			Each token on the board is worth the number of points equal to the
			section of the board on which it is located.<br>
			A player's score for his own prestige is the <b><i>sum</i></b> of his
			two highest valued tokens on the board.<br>
			A player's score for his supporting prestige is the <b><i>product</i></b>
			of the two highest valued tokens on the board belonging to the player
			he supported.<br>
			A player's total score for a turn is the sum of his own prestige and
			his supporting prestige.<br><br>
			<i>For example:  The Blue player chose to secretly support the Yellow
			player.  At the end of the turn there were blue tokens on the board
			of value 3, 3 and 4, and yellow tokens on the board of value 1, 2,
			and 3.  The Blue player would score (3+4) = 7 points for his own
			prestige and would score (2x3) = 6 points for Yellow's prestige.  So,
			Blue would score (7+6) = 13 points for this turn.</i><br><br>
			After scoring, each player retrieves their tokens from the board
			and the next turn starts with the players again choosing which other
			player to secretly support.
			<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="End of Game">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>End of Game</u></b></font><br>
			The game ends after the number of turns equal to the number of players
			in the game.  The winner is the player who has scored the most prestige
			points during the game.
			<br>]]>
		</section>
	</section>

	<section title="Interface Details">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Interface Details</u></b></font>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Main Board">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Main Board</u></b></font><br>
			On the left side of the screen is the main board where the tokens
			will be played.<br>
			The top part of the main board is also where the selection of secret
			support is made during that phase of the game.<br>
			The last piece to have been placed on the board will be indicated
			by a black halo around it.<br>
			The last piece to have been moved on the board will be indicated by
			a white halo around it.
			<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Scoring Track">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Scoring Track</u></b></font><br>
			Running around the board is the scoring track where the scoring
			tokens for each player indicate the current number of prestige
			points accumulated by the players.  The 0 space is in the upper
			left corner and points accumulate clockwise around the board.<br><br>
			Anytime during the game, mousing over a scoring marker will display
			the score received by that player during the most recent turn.
			Two lines will be drawn that indicate the points scored for the
			player's own prestige and his supporter's prestige points.
			<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Player Areas">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Player Areas</u></b></font><br>
			On the right side of the screen are the player areas.  Each player
			area shows the tokens that have not yet been placed on the board
			and shows a rose which indicates which other player was chosen for
			secret support.<br><br>
			A player always sees his own player area at the top of the column,
			with player order going down the screen.<br><br>
			During the selection phase, a player who has not yet chosen another
			player to secretly support will display a question mark on the selection rose.
			Once the selection has been made, the icon will change to an exclamation point.<br><br>
			During the selection phase and the rounds, a player will only see
			his own secret selection, with the other players showing a neutral,
			gray rose.  During scoring, all players will see all of the chosen
			secret selections.
			<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Choosing Support">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Choosing Support</u></b></font><br>
			During the support selection phase, cards indicating all of the
			other players in the game will be drawn at the top of the main
			board.  Clicking on one of them will select that player to be
			supported for the current turn.
			<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Placing tokens">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Placing Tokens</u></b></font><br>
			When it is a player's turn to place a token on the board, mousing
			over the board will show where the token will be placed.  Clicking
			will place the token on the board.
			<br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Moving tokens">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u><br>Moving Tokens</u></b></font><br>
			When it is a player's turn to move a token on the board, mousing
			over a piece on the board will highlight it and draw a line to
			show where the piece would be moved to.  Clicking will slide the token
			on the board.
			<br>]]>
		</section>
	</section>
</rules>
