<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--

This is a DTD description of a rules file.  However, since NanoXML that JOGRE
uses doesn't support DTD descriptions, it is given in a comment.

<!DOCTYPE rules [
<!ELEMENT rules (section+)>
<!ATTLIST rules content (text | text/html | text/rtf) "text"
				title CDATA #REQUIRED>
	<!ELEMENT section (section+ | CDATA)>
	<!ATTLIST title CDATA #IMPLIED>
]>

Notes: The "rules" element *must* have a title even though that title is never
       shown to the users.  If the title isn't there, then nothing will display
       in the rules window.

       Sections are not required to have a title, but only sections with titles
       will show up in the index'd tree list.

       NanoXML doesn't support mixing elements and CDATA inside of an element,
       and so non-title'd sections allow that functionality.

       You can embed sections within sections and they will show up in the
       tree as subsections.

       The <![CDATA[ ... ]]> verbiage is needed for text that uses HTML tags within
       it.  Without them, NanoXML would try to parse them as XML and fail.  For plain
       text rules files, you don't need them.
-->

<rules content="text/html" title="Rules">
	<section title="Introduction">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Introduction</u></b></font><br>
		Points Total was designed by PyroMyth games in 2005.<br><br>
		The rules are available as one of the "free games" at their web site
		http://www.pyromythgames.com/<br><br>
		The star used to indicate first-player status was drawn by Sergio I. Rivera.
		It is in the public domain and is available from http://www.openclipart.org/<br><br>
		All other graphics drawn by Richard Walter and are put into the public
		domain.<br><br>
		The program was written by Richard Walter (rwalter42@yahoo.com)
		<br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Playing the Game">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Playing the Game</u></b></font><br>
		Each player starts with a set of four pieces, each with a value and
		arrows drawn on it.<br><br>
		On a player's turn, he must place one of his pieces on any space on the
		board that does not already have a piece on it.  It may be oriented in
		any direction.<br><br>
		The player scores points of the value of the piece plus the values of
		the other spaces/pieces that the arrows on the placed piece are pointing
		toward.<br><br>
		After all players have placed all of their pieces, the board is cleared
		and the next round begins with the next player starting.<br><br>
		The game is over after all players have been the starting player once.
		The player with the highest total score is the winner.
		<br>]]>
	</section>


	<section title="Screen Layout">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Screen Layout</u></b></font><br>
			On the left side of the screen is the 4x4 board where pieces are
			played to score points.  On the right side of the screen are the
			unplayed pieces that all players have available and their scores.<br><br>
			There is a star at the top of each column of pieces that indicates
			which players have had their chance playing first in the round.  A
			player which has a star has <b>not</b> yet played first.  The player
			with the green halo around the star is the player who went first this
			round. When all players have had their turn playing first, the game
			is over.
			<br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Placing a piece">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u><br>Placing a piece</u></b></font><br>
		When it is your turn, clicking on one of your pieces in the right
		side of the screen will select that piece to be played on the board.<br><br>
		Moving the mouse over the board will show the potential piece that
		will be placed.<br><br>
		The piece can be rotated clockwise & counter-clockwise by using either:<br>
		&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;* left & right arrow keys<br>
		&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;* 'z' and 'x' keys<br>
		&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;* left & right arrow keys on the numeric keypad<br><br>
		Clicking on the main board will place the piece.<br><br>
		<br>]]>
	</section>

</rules>
