<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--

This is A DTD description of a rules file.  However, since NanoXML that JOGRE
uses doesn't support DTD descriptions, it is given in a comment.

<!DOCTYPE rules [
<!ELEMENT rules (section+)>
<!ATTLIST rules content (text | text/html | text/rtf) "text"
				title CDATA #REQUIRED>
	<!ELEMENT section (section+ | CDATA)>
	<!ATTLIST title CDATA #IMPLIED>
]>

Notes: The "rules" element *must* have a title even though that title is never
       shown to the users.  If the title isn't there, then nothing will display
       in the rules window.

       Sections are not required to have a title, but only sections with titles
       will show up in the index'd tree list.

       NanoXML doesn't support mixing elements and CDATA inside of an element,
       and so non-title'd sections allow that functionality.

       You can embed sections within sections and they will show up in the
       tree as subsections.

       The <![CDATA[ ... ]]> verbiage is needed for text that uses HTML tags within
       it.  Without them, NanoXML would try to parse them as XML and fail.  For plain
       text rules files, you don't need them.
-->

<rules content="text/html" title="Rules">
	<section title="Introduction">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Introduction</u></b></font><br>
		The game of Abstrac was designed by David Parlett.<br>
		It is described in the book "Original Card Games".<br><br>
		The card images used in the game were drawn by Nicu Buculei.  They are in the
		public domain and are available from http://www.openclipart.org/<br><br>
		The card suit images used on the left of the claimed grid were drawn by Guillaume Boitel.  They are
		in the public domain and are available from http://www.openclipart.org/<br><br>
		The star image used to indicate claimed cards was drawn by Sergio I. Rivera.  It is
		in the public domain and is available from http://www.openclipart.org/<br><br>
		The program was written by Richard Walter (rwalter42@yahoo.com)<br><br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Overview">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Overview</u></b></font><br>
		Abstrac is a card game for 2 players.<br><br>
		Players take turns picking cards from the deck.  Points are scored for sets
		(cards of the same values of different suits) and runs (cards of the
		same suit that are of consecutive values) collected.<br><br>
		But each card a player takes increases the values of his opponent's sets and runs...<br><br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Deck">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Deck</u></b></font><br>
		Abstrac is played with a deck of 24 cards using only the cards 9 through Ace.<br><br>]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Playing the Game">
		<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Playing the Game</u></b></font><br>
		The 24 cards are shuffled and dealt out face up between both players.<br><br>
		Players alternate turns, taking 1, 2, or 3 cards from the top of the deck.<br><br>
		]]>
	</section>

	<section title="Scoring">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Scoring</u></b></font><br>
			After all of the cards have been claimed, scoring occurs.<br><br>
			A player scores points for sets and runs.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Sets">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Sets</u></b></font><br>
			A set is 3 or 4 cards of the same value, such as 3 Jacks, or 4 Aces.<br><br>
			A set of 3 is worth 2 points.<br>
			A set of 4 is worth 8 points.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Runs">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Runs</u></b></font><br>
			A run is 3 or more cards of the same suit in consecutive order.  For example,
			the 9, 10 and Jack of Hearts is a run of 3.<br><br>
			A run of 3 is worth 3 points.<br>
			A run of 4 is worth 4 points.<br>
			A run of 5 is worth 6 points.<br>
			A run of 6 is worth 12 points.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section>
			<![CDATA[
			After totalling the points made from sets and runs, a player multiplies that
			total by the number of cards taken by his <b><i>opponent</i></b>.  For example,
			if a player scored 12 points with sets and runs, and took 15 cards to do it,
			then is total score would be 12 * 9 = 108, because if he took 15 cards, then
			his opponent took only 9 cards.<br><br>
			Whichever player has the larger final score is the winner.<br><br>]]>
		</section>
	</section>

	<section title="Interface Details">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Interface Details</u></b></font><br><br>
			The table contains two grids that show which cards have been taken by each
			player separated by the deck layed out between them.  Both players see their
			cards indicated at the top of the screen and their opponent's cards indicated
			at the bottom of the screen.<br><br>
			At the beginning of a game, the grids are empty and all 24 cards are layed out
			in the middle of the table.<br><br>
			Each square of the grid shows a different symbol to indicate a player's holdings.<br><br>
			* A star indicates a card that has been taken by that player.  Stars with green
			backgrounds indicate cards that were taken on the most recent turn.<br>
			* A grey dash indicates that the card has been taken by the opponent.<br>
			* An empty square indicates that the card is still in the deck and has not been
			claimed by either player.<br><br>
			On a player's turn, he must select one, two, or three cards from the top of
			the deck.  As the mouse is moved over the deck the selected cards will be
			highlighted.  Also, a transparent star will be placed in the player's grid to
			indicate the selected cards.
			Clicking the mouse button will select the cards and move them to the player's grid.<br><br>
			The scores on the right and bottom of the grid indicate the scores for runs and sets
			taken.  The boxed area in the lower right corner shows the total of the
			points for sums and sets, the number of cards taken by the opponent, and the
			current grand total.<br><br>
			]]>
		</section>
	</section>

	<section title="Customization">
		<section>
			<![CDATA[<font size="+2"><b><u>Customization</u></b></font><br>
			Many parameters of the game are cusomizable from the game.properties file.
			This file is editable with any text editor.<br><br>
			<i>player.colour.x</i> - Can be used to change the color of the players.<br><br>
			<i>display.hand.cardSpacing</i> - The number of pixels between left-hand edges
			of two cards in the hand.<br><br>
			<i>display.hand.selectYOffset</i> - The number of pixels to move a selectable
			card when moused over.<br><br>
			<i>display.taken.digitSpacing</i> - The number of pixels between digits of multi-digit
			numbers in the score area.<br><br>
			<i>display.taken.HSpacing</i> - The number of pixels between each column of the score
			panel<br><br>
			<i>display.taken.VSpacing</i> - The number of pixels between each row of the score panel.<br><br>]]>
		</section>

		<section title="Customizing Images">
			<![CDATA[<font size="+1"><b><u>Customizing Images</u></b></font><br>
			The game.properties file contains entries for images used in the game.  You can
			customize the game by making new image files and setting the appropriate image.x
			line in the game.properties file to point to your new image.<br><br>
			Each image line contains a filename followed by the size of the file.  If you change an image
			file, make sure that you change the size as well.<br><br>
			<i>image.0</i> - The icon used in the window.  This must be 16x16 pixels.<br><br>
			<i>image.1</i> - The cards used in the game.  This is an array of images of the
			cards.  You can change the size of the cards, but each card must be the same size
			and the cards must remain in the same relative position.  (ie: the 9 of diamonds
			must be in the upper left corner, with the 9 of spades below it.).<br><br>
			<i>image.2</i> - The symbols used to indicate the various parts of the scoring grid.
			This is a horizontal row of 14 symbols<br><br>
			<i>image.3</i> - The digits used to draw the scores.  This includes the multiplication
			sign and the equals sign.<br><br>]]>
		</section>
	</section>
</rules>
